

# KATIE BERGMANN



graphic designer & front-end developer

E-MAIL ADDRESS PHONE

kbergmann15@my.whitworth.edu

25324 232nd Ave SE Maple Valley, WA 98038

425 • 495 • 1636

# **EDUCATION**

## GRAPHIC DESIGN (BA)

Minor: Psychology & Art History GPA: 3.8

Whitworth University Spokane, Washington 2011-2014

# **DESIGN SKILLS**

## ADOBE PRODUCTS

**TYPOGRAPHY** 

LAYOUT DESIGN

WEB DESIGN

HTML / CSS / JAVASCRIPT

**ADVERTISING** 

PHOTOGRAPHY

BRANDING / LOGO DESIGN

DRAWING

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm currently finishing my last semester at Whitworth University, one of the top students in my graphic design program and have a passion for hexcodes, grids and typography! While I've been in school, I have developed strong skills in the design of logos, layout design, package design, illustrations and web design (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript). I am confident in myself as a consistent and functional designer. I would love to gain more extensive hands-on experience in the field and to have the opportunity to work for a company that matches my enthusiasim for modern design and innovation!

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## SSEKO GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN

Sseko Designs, Portland OR, Summer 2015

Utilized Adobe Products to create a wide variety of advertisments, infographs, emails and sales campaigns for Sseko's footwear collection and handbag lines.

- Photoshop
- llustrator
- InDesign

- Marketing Strategies
- Design Psychology

## NATSIHI YEARBOOK GRAPHIC DESIGN EDITOR

Whitworth University, Spokane Wa, Fall 2014-Summer 2015

Worked closely with photo and writing editors. Utilized InDesign combinding text and imagery to create an innovative and cohesive theme throughout the yearbook.

- InDesign
- llustrator
- Photoshop

- ${\color{red} \bullet} \ Layout \ Design$
- $\bullet \ Typography \ Design$
- Photography



# KATIE BERGMANN



graphic designer & front-end developer

E-MAIL ADDRESS PHONE

kbergmann15@my.whitworth.edu

25324 232nd Ave SE Maple Valley, WA 98038

425 • 495 • 1636

## SOFTWARE

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

ADOBE INDESIGN

ADOBE LIGHTROOM

ADOBE DREAMWEAVER

ADOBE FIREWORKS

WORDPRESS

# **AWARDS**

## ENHANCED ART TALENT AWARD

Whitworth University Spokane, Washington 2011-2014

# REFERENCES

\* AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### LITERARY JOURNAL DESIGN EDITOR

Whitworth University, Spokane Wa, Fall 2011-Summer 2012

Designed layouts, text, and photos centered around the student body and their literary works. Worked closely with a small team during weekly meetings to produce a local literary journal.

- Photography & Layout Design
- InDesign

## WHITWORTH COSTA RICA CENTER DESIGNER & PHOTOGRAPHER

Whitworth University, San Heredia Costa Rica, 2012

Combined photography, design, and text to amplify a Costa Rican hotels room and capture unique aspects of the culture.

Photography

- Poster Design
- Lightroom & Photoshop
- · Interior Design

#### **FREELANCE**

Spokane Wa, 2012-2015

- Fluevog Soprano Carey Footwear Advertisment
- · Whitworth Jubilation poster designs and logos
- · Adopted Pirates Club poster designs and logos
- Book cover posters for Cedar Tree Christian School
- Resume designs and monograms for private clients

# **INTERESTS**

- CrossFit
- Gymnastics
- Hiking & the Outdoors
- Exploring the city to find the best food places & coffee joints